jewsforjesus.org 2016-10-29

# Privacy Policy - Jews for Jesus

## Privacy Policy

Jews for Jesus has created the following privacy statement in order to disclose our information-gathering and dissemination practices for the web sites attached to jewsforjesus.org domain and all sub-domains thereof, including but not limited to: [www.jewsforjesus.org](http://www.jewsforjesus.org/ "www.jewsforjesus.org"), [store.jewsforjesus.org](http://store.jewsforjesus.org/ "store.jewsforjesus.org").

### Use of Personal Information

Jews for Jesus does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically and knowingly provide such information. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from information request forms, subscription forms, surveys, online transactions, and virtual greeting cards.

Users also should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected, such as your IP address. We may use the IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Web sites. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

Jews for Jesus reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the sites. Jews for Jesus will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties, unless otherwise legally required to do so.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Jews for Jesus uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart in our online bookstore, and may from time to time use cookies for other purposes.

### Policies Concerning Minors

Jews for Jesus does not knowingly collect personally identifiable or contact information from any person known by us to be under the age of 18 unless we receive prior written parental consent.

Jews for Jesus does not knowingly contact or maintain a correspondence with any person under the age of 18 without prior written parental consent.

IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 18, WE MUST HAVE WRITTEN PERMISSION FROM YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN BEFORE YOU MAY DO ANY OF THE FOLLOWING ON THE JEWS FOR JESUS WEB SITES:

  * SUBMIT PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF OR OTHERS
  * BUY ANYTHING
  * MAKE A DONATION

### Public Forums

This site may now or in the future make chat rooms and/or bulletin boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in a public chat or on a bulletin board becomes public information. You should exercise caution when disclosing personal information.

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Jews for Jesus uses a secure server for handling online purchases and donations.

### Links to Other Sites

Jews for Jesus is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites to which we may link.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our use of personal information, or other policies of this web site, [contact us here](http://jewsforjesus.org/index.php?Itemid=1735 "contact us here").

If you wish to submit or change personal information such as a name and address, or to request or opt-out of receiving communications from us, contact us at:

Jews for Jesus  
60 Haight St.  
San Francisco, CA 94102
